[{"answer": "I want to feel like I broke into the studio and took over and made them mad.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "What on earth will Bill Maher say tonight?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "But isn't the reality, that with an election coming, just as the president hinted today, I mean if I was a Republican, the way to beat President Obama, the way that the job figures stand at the moment, 9.2 percent, the state of the economy generally, turmoil around the country continuing -- the way to probably beat him is to take him on on the economy.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "The party out of power always threatens this, you know?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "No probably about it.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "It's not in their interest to do a deal, is it?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, I like this quote from Warren Buffett who says the way to get rid of the deficit, we should pass a law that says any time there's a deficit of more than 3 percent of GDP, all sitting members of Congress are ineligible for reelection.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Isn't it the Congress' job to present a jobs bill?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Well, if you're talking about social mobility, yes.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "So it's all surprising to me that the people governing the country pander to that by this rhetoric of everything has to make a profit because that's the way you have a yardstick of success here, isn't it?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Because it shows we're falling behind China.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Why is it scary?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "But we would have to reconfigure all of our priorities.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Can America afford to see everything economically, militarily and so on as a threat in the way it has before?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Many Americans, it seems to me -- I mean you say this stuff and I bet you get deluged with people calling you unpatriotic, un-American.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Who's the threat that's going to invade us?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "What's patriotic is wanting your country to succeed.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "But, I mean, is it time that America completely changed its philosophy on these things?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "None.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "How many do the Chinese have?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "A hundred and 25,000 millionaires in Shanghai.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "I would meet a gun to my head.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Palin or Bachmann?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Is it possible in the current climate?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "That's a great question.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Is America more or less racist now since Obama has been in power?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, you know, hopefully Mitt Romney.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Are there other any of the Republican candidates so far that have emerged that you would see as potentially not life threatening?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Jimmy Carter was an amazingly principled president.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Has there ever been a president in your lifetime who has been properly principled in your eyes?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Well, not that, is there's a kind of expectation from this mass populace that you have to do certain things.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "It attracts criticism?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "You know I love him.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "How do you think Obama is doing as president?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Is it, though?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "If a Democrat gets in and we don't attempt Democratic policy.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "What should he be doing right now?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "I think I'm just practical.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "But what tag are you proudest of putting yourself to?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "You hate their ideology, don't you think?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "But do you -- I mean you're a Democrat?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I mean I'm certainly more in line with their thinking.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "How would you describe yourself?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Do you vote?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Almost always.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Democrat?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Ever voted Republican?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I voted for McCain in the 2000 primary.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "When?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Part of is that jury, trial of your peers.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Is part of it television cameras in the court?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "They cannot appreciate nuance.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "People don't even get that, right?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "It's a combination of apathy and atheist, yes.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "This is an apathetic, atheist, right?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "No, that's not right at all.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "AHER: No.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Is it bordering on any form of accuracy?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I was never Jewish.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Then what happened?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Can you stop being a Catholic?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I'm with him, 6.9.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Where are you?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "When I was a kid, we went to church.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "How did your parents react to your ap-atheism?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "It has been -- if there was a God for comedians, he may have been raining down upon us, yes.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "If you had prayed, would you have prayed for the kind of news cycle we have had, from Weiner-gate to Schwarzenegger-gate?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Much more, because I'm good at it now.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Do you get as much fun of that now as you always used to?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I don't understand Twitter when people just tell you what they're doing.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "But do you feel a pressure, even when you're doing that, to be endlessly funny?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "You don't troll for the ladies like Mr. Weiner?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "She would expect me to ask these kind of questions.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Aren't you going to get in trouble with your wife for talking about marriage this way?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "I know Charlie a bit.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "When you look at someone like Charlie Sheen, what do you honestly think of his behavioral pattern?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "I said that, it was a joke.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "And is it true that you honestly believe you only go there for the food?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "I went in the grotto.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "You went in the grotto?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "This job?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "Is this part of the trick of show business, knowing when to leave the party?", "qSentId": 794}, {"answer": "But I didn't think Larry was diminished in any way.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 797, "question": "Being able to choose it -- have your own destiny?", "qSentId": 796}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110711pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 806}]